Idufashe Tharcissie

Kigali City, Rwanda



tharcissieidufashe@gmail.com





linkedin.com/in/idufashe-tharcissie-19a3311ab



Summary

2 years of experience in software development and Information technology. Experienced front-end and back-end developer trained in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Python, Django, and Nextjs. Moreover, Maintains and supports computer networks, resolves problems associated with software and hardware errors.

Experience



Software Engineer

Bhala

teams

May 2020 - Sep 2021 (1 year 5 months) Designed and developed web applications individually and in

Security Analyst

Broadcasters of ICT

Oct 2017 - Feb 2020 (2 years 5 months)

Maintained and supported computer networks

- * Resolved issues related to Windows and network connectivity
- * Resolved problem associated to software and hardware errors.

Education



University of Rwanda

Bachelor's Degree, Information Technology 2017 - 2021



Saint Vincent Muhoza Secondary School (SVMSS)

High school Diploma, Math, Physics, and Computer science 2013 - 2015

Licenses & Certifications



Python programming workshop. - PWS Africa Group

Certificate of Excellence, Advanced programming in web Application **Development.** - Moringa School

Internet of Things (IOT) in Agriculture, Transport, and Energy. - STES GROUP

Front- End Web D evelopment w ith React - The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology

coursera .org /veri f y/Y PC JQN544H C L

- Front- End Web U I Framew orks and Tools: Bootstrap 4 The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology co u rsera.o rg/v eri f y /W4ZNGGYAMV Q K
- Write Professional Emails in English Georgia Institute of Technology coursera.org/verify/N3NLW7MRHUJ3
- Speak English Professionally Georgia Institute of Technology coursera.org/verify/E8FEFMSS8RXM
- Google IT Support Professional Certificate Google coursera.org/verify/professional-cert/RNLC7C6QABKH

Skills

attention to detail • communication skills • critical thinking • english • french • self-starter • Teamwork • Self Learning • Love Of Learning

Projects

BRS-Care - web Application - March 2021 <u>link to the website</u> BRS-care helps people to search for house to rent or buy and even let you publish your house.

Implemented backend and front-end.

ProjectApp - Web Application - January 2021 - <u>link to the website</u> An app that enables to see the different projects posted by users. You can view and rate them. Moreover, you can post also your projects to be viewed and rated.

Implemented backend and front-end

Github-Info - Web Application - November 2020 - <u>link to the website</u> This is a simple web-based application that helps to retrieve users' git hub repositories with their detailed information.

Implemented backend and front-end.

Password_Locker - Application - November 2020 - <u>github link</u> password locker is an application that helps to store our credentials from different accounts.

Implemented the backend.